You can't escape your dreams.
Eye for an Eye is a horror film directed by Colin Tilley.
Anna, grieving the sudden death of her parents, relocates from New York to a
small Florida town to live with the grandmother she has never met.
Isolated, vulnerable, and in need of friends, she finds
brief solace in the company of two local teens.
But when she becomes complicit to their unforgivable act of
violence, she finds herself ensnared by Mr.
Sandman – the twisted soul of a tormented child who haunts bullies’ dreams before feasting on their eyeballs when
they finally wake - Anna must right her wrong before becoming a victim of this gruesome curse.
Anna, played by Whitney Peak.
Patti, played by Golda Rosheuvel.
Shawn, played by Finn Bennett.
Julie Cross, played by Laken Giles.
May, played by S. Epatha Merkerson.
Conner, played by Carson Minniear.
Eye for an Eye is a 2025 American horror film, directed by Colin Tilley in his feature
directorial debut, from a screenplay by Elisa Victoria and Michael Tully.
It stars Whitney Peak, S.
Epatha Merkerson, Golda Rosheuvel, Finn Bennett and Laken Giles.
It was released on June 20, 2025, by Vertical.
The film explores themes of based on graphic novel, entity,
supernatural creature, dream logic, supernatural investigation.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.